let questions = [
    {
        numb:1.,
        question:'Which of the following is the most impoetant language for data science life cycle',
        answer:'B. R',
        options: [
            'A. ruby',
            'B. R',
            'C. java',
            'D. none'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2.,
        question:'A collectionof information about a related topic is reffered as a..........',
        answer:'A. visualisation',
        options:[
            'A. visualisation',
            'B. analysis',
            'C. conclusion',
            'D. data'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3.,
        question:'To find the....... you put all numbers in order fromleast to greatest and find the the numbefr that is in the middle',
        answer:'A. median',
        options:[
            'A. median',
            'B. mode',
            'C. mean',
            'D. range'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4.,
        question:'A relation between two or more variables is referred to as a..........',
        answer:'A. Trend',
        options:[
            'A. Trend',
            'B. spike',
            'C. All of the above',
            'D. none of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5.,
        question:'A graphical representation of a data set is refered to as a..........',
        answer:'C. Investigative cycle',
        options:[
            'A. visualization',
            'B. data set',
            'C. Investigative cycle',
            'D. none'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6.,
        question:'data that sits outside the trend is reffered to as a.......',
        answer:'D. both (1) & (2)',
        options:[
            'A. outiler',
            'B. trend',
            'C. spike',
            'D. both (1) & (2)'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7.,
        question:'R is an......... programming language?',
        answer:'B. open source',
        options:[
            'A. GPL',
            'B. open source',
            'C. close source',
            'D. definite source'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8.,
        question:'What is the primary goal of data science',
        answer:'B. extracting actionable insights from data',
        options:[
            'A. Data storage',
            'B. extracting actionable insights from data',
            'C. creating data visualizations',
            'D. software development'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9.,
        question:'which EDA technique is useful for identifying missing values in a dataset',
        answer:'D. missing data matrix',
        options:[
            'A. boxplot',
            'B. scatter plot',
            'C. bar chart',
            'D. missing data matrix'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10.,
        question:'what is the alternative name for the airthmatic mean?',
        answer:'B. Average',
        options:[
            'A. Central tedency',
            'B. Average',
            'C. median',
            'D. Mode'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:11.,
        question:'Vectors come in two parts:',
        answer:'A. a atomic vector and list',
        options:[
            'A. a atomic vector and list',
            'B. a atomic number and array',
            'C. a atomic number and matrix',
            'D. none',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:12.,
        question:'Which of the following is not a machine learning algorithm',
        answer:'C. svg',
        options:[
            'A. svm',
            'B. random forest',
            'C. svg',
            'D. none',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:13.,
        question:'Data that outsides the trend is refered to as a ',
        answer:'A. outlier',
        options: [
            'A. outlier',
            'B. trend',
            'C. spike ',
            'D. infinity',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:14.,
        question:'R is an ....... type of programming language',
        answer:'B. open source',
        options:[
            'A. gpl',
            'B. open source',
            'C. closed source',
            'D. definite source',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:15.,
        question:'What is the primary key of data science',
        answer:'D. extracting actionable insights from data',
        options:[
            'A. data storage',
            'B. software development',
            'C. creating data visualization',
            'D. extracting actionable insights from data',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:16.,
        question:'What is the basic block of nueral network',
        answer:'A. neuron',
        options:[
            'A. nueron',
            'B. feature',
            'C. instance',
            'D. layer',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:17.,
        question:'Data science is the process of diverse set of data through',
        answer:'D. all of the above',
        options:[
            'A. organizing data ',
            'B. processing data',
            'C. linear aggression',
            'D. all of the above',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:18.,
        question:'A method is used to make vector of repeated values ',
        answer:'C. rep()',
        options:[
            'A. oread()',
            'B. data()',
            'C. rep()',
            'D. view()',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:19.,
        question:'Data fishing is sometime to refered as ',
        answer:'B. data dregding',
        options:[
            'A. data bagging',
            'B. data dregding',
            'C. data merging',
            'D. none',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:20.,
        question:'Which is one of the significant data science skills',
        answer:'A. statistics',
        options:[
            'A. statistics',
            'B. data',
            'C. machine learning',
            'D. all of the above'
        ]
    }
]